<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Yet another blog restart</title>
    <link>https://pseyfert.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Yet another blog restart</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 23:22:00 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://pseyfert.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Bad self-checkout procedure made worse by bad UI</title>
      <link>https://pseyfert.github.io/2025/11/bad-self-checkout-procedure-made-worse-by-bad-ui/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 23:22:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://pseyfert.github.io/2025/11/bad-self-checkout-procedure-made-worse-by-bad-ui/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;To make this post a bit LinkedIn compatible (why?), let&amp;rsquo;s open with something business:&#xA;The self-checkout cash registers at our local supermarket have &amp;lsquo;TOSHIBA&amp;rsquo; written on them.&#xA;I assume in some business to business negotiations that was agreed upon and effectively Toshiba is paying for having their brand name displayed on the terminal (or the supermarket would&amp;rsquo;ve needed to pay more to receive unbranded terminals). And I think this deal backfires because the UI has some flaws which make the product appear poorly designed or tested - so poorly that I&amp;rsquo;m writing a blog post about them. (Or maybe all publicity is good publicity, whatever, it&amp;rsquo;s not like I expect many readers).&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Yes, the skin breathes but does it breath?</title>
      <link>https://pseyfert.github.io/2025/08/yes-the-skin-breathes-but-does-it-breath/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2025 18:26:57 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://pseyfert.github.io/2025/08/yes-the-skin-breathes-but-does-it-breath/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Given my activities in club during highschool years, I attended a couple of&#xA;first aid courses, refreshers, paramedic courses, etc as standardized by&#xA;various volunteer organizations in Germany. At a few occasions, breathing,&#xA;oxygen processing by the body and such got discussed. And one of the teachers&#39;&#xA;points usually was that the body gets all its oxygen through the air that we&#xA;breath into the lung and none through the skin and that it was an urban myth that the skin&#xA;breaths.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Code I wouldn&#39;t put into production anymore - manual auto vectorization</title>
      <link>https://pseyfert.github.io/2024/07/code-i-wouldnt-put-into-production-anymore-manual-auto-vectorization/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2024 21:21:17 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://pseyfert.github.io/2024/07/code-i-wouldnt-put-into-production-anymore-manual-auto-vectorization/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Let&amp;rsquo;s be clear, this is no work of my own. It is based on what &lt;a href=&#34;http://cds.cern.ch/record/2668250&#34;&gt;Florian Lemaitre&lt;/a&gt; once explained to me and &lt;a href=&#34;https://gitlab.cern.ch/lhcb/LHCb/-/commit/ccd24ee9d4ad5a05a82886223eb1f67eb782a24d&#34;&gt;committed to the LHCb software&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;sup id=&#34;fnref:1&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#fn:1&#34; class=&#34;footnote-ref&#34; role=&#34;doc-noteref&#34;&gt;1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;&#xA;It was something that I had been wondering about for a while and hadn&amp;rsquo;t found resources on the internet.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;why-not-put-it-in-production-anymore&#34;&gt;Why not put it in production anymore?&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Thinking of the code that I write these days for production, I&amp;rsquo;m afraid&#xA;it&amp;rsquo;s way more important to be able to debug and maintain the code base than to&#xA;squeeze the last CPU cycle out of the performance. Also from a developer time&#xA;point of view, the opportunity cost for writing these blocks is way too high to&#xA;justify (imo).&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
